let questionBank = [{
        question: "When was the Saxon Palace built?",
        option: ["1639-1642", "1611", "2022", "1945"],
        answer: "1639-1642"
    }, {
        question: "Where IS the Saxon Palace located now?",
        option: ["Gdansk", "London", "No-where. It's destroyed.", "Warsaw"],
        answer: "No-where. It's destroyed."
    }, {
        question: "When will the Saxon Palace be restored?",
        option: ["1945", "2100", "2023-2030", "2018"],
        answer: "2023-2030"
    },
    {
        question : "Which famous pianist was living in the Saxon Palace?",
        option : ["Chopin", "Bach", "Vivaldi", "Mozart"],
        answer : "Chopin"
    }, {
        question : "When was the Saxon Palace destroyed by Germans?",
        option : ["1918", "1900", "1989", "1945"],
        answer: "1945"
    }, {
        question : "What is located on the Saski Square now?",
        option : ["Ice-cream truck", "Tomb of the Unknown Soldier", "Coffee Shop", "Nothing"],
        answer: "Tomb of the Unknown Soldier"
    }, {
        question : "What was located NEXT to the Saxon Palace?",
        option : ["Grocery Shop", "Brühl Palace", "Airport", "Coding Department"],
        answer: "Brühl Palace"
    }, {
        question : "What was located IN the Saxon Palace?",
        option : ["Grocery Shop", "Brühl Palace", "Airport", "Coding Department"],
        answer: "Coding Department"
    }, {
        question : "Which army was operated in the Saxon Palace in 1918-1939?",
        option : ["The Polish Army", "The German Army", "The Russian Army", "NATO"],
        answer: "The Polish Army"
    }, {
        question : "What architectural concept is connected to the Saxon Palace?",
        option : ["Warsaw's water pipes system", "Saxon Axis with the Garden, Theatre and the Iron Gate", "None", "Love Parade tents"],
        answer: "Saxon Axis with the Garden, Theatre and the Iron Gate"
    },
]